

stzito@gmail.com



415-640-4576



stzito.github.io



SF Bay Area, CA

I'm Stephen Zito,

UX/UI Designer specializing in innovative and elegant user experiences for digital products across mobile, web, and proprietary interfaces.

Collaborating with designers, engineers, and stakeholders on a mission to make products accessible and enjoyable for users from all walks of life is my passion.

Skillset



Photoshop



Illustrator



InDesign



Sketch



InVision



Framer / Principle



HTML / CSS



JavaScript

Education

San Francisco State University
BA Industrial Arts: Web/UI Design

Honors: Magna Cum Laude

Class of 2009

Designed and developed responsive websites for University and clients, including design and prototyping of mobile and proprietary software interfaces.

Experience

Contract Design • Sr. UX/UI & Visual Designer

2013 - 2017

- User-centric creative design and planning for companies and non-profit community organizations.
- Design of mobile, web, and proprietary applications through established UI and UX best practices.
- User research, user flows, wireframes, prototyping, and testing for products and services.
 Clean, contemporary visual design and branding for digital and print mediums.

Vergence Labs • Lead UX/UI Designer

2012 - 2013

- Responsive consumer-facing web design for online store and social media platform.
- UX and UI Design for native mobile and web-based applications.
- Research and product design for consumer wearable HD video glasses.
- Unified aesthetic for physical products and software.
- Branding and Visual Design across multiple properties.
- Focus on hardware/software user retention and augmented reality applications.

Tapjoy • UX/UI Designer

2011 - 2012

- Creation of web and mobile product flows, design, and user interface.
- Collaboration with engineers in implementing new designs and concepts.
- Redesign of mobile and web user experience and aesthetics for consumer and B2B products.
- Conceiving UX solutions and defining product flow.
- UI Design for Tapjoy mobile games and products.
- Establishing and maintaining the Tapjoy brand.

50 Cubes • UX/UI Designer

2011

- Interface design for multiple leading Facebook games on mobile and web platforms.
- Design of main game screens and interface elements.
- Complete interface re-design for iPad game port.
- Creation of vector and raster game graphics.
- Promotion of game updates through daily marketing images.

Tesla Motors • UX/UI Design Intern

2010

- Design and production of interface elements for a high-resolution touch screen.
- Design of vector-based interface icons with attention to size and scalability.
- Creation of color palette and style guide to unify icons and UI elements.
- Collaboration with engineers in interface features and aesthetics.